<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game>
		<path>./Broforce.lnk</path>
		<name>Broforce</name>
		<desc>When evil threatens the world, the world calls on Broforce - an under-funded, over-powered paramilitary organization dealing exclusively in excessive force. Brace your loins with up to four players to run ‘n’ gun as dozens of different bros and eliminate the opposing terrorist forces that threaten our way of life.</desc>
		<image>./images/Broforce-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20140407T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Free Lives</developer>
		<publisher>Devolver Digital</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./DuckGame.lnk</path>
		<name>Duck Game</name>
		<desc>Enter the futuristic year of 1984, an age where ducks run wild in a frantic battle for glory. Win over the crowd and gain a following by blasting your feathered friends with Shotguns, Net Guns, Mind Control Rays, Saxophones, Magnet Guns, and pretty much anything else a duck could use as a weapon. One hit and you're roasted. This is DUCK GAME. Don't blink. 

2 to 4 PLAYERS in either Local Multiplayer Couch Combat, or NEW Online Play! 
Single Player challenge mode 
Easy to pick up, emphasizing strategy over twitch reaction 
50+ Levels, 50+ Weapons 
Level Editor</desc>
		<image>./images/DuckGame-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/DuckGame-marquee.png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20150604T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Landon Podbielski</developer>
		<publisher>Adult Swim Games</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Shooter</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SonicRoboBlast2.lnk</path>
		<name>Sonic Robo Blast 2</name>
		<desc>Sonic Robo Blast 2 is a 3D sonic fan game made on the Doom engine.</desc>
		<image>./images/SonicRoboBlast2-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20200511T000000</releasedate>
		<genre>Platform, Unofficial</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game id="295542">
		<path>./epic_EnterTheGrungeon.cmd</path>
		<name>Enter the Gungeon</name>
		<desc>Enter the Gungeon is a bullet hell dungeon crawler following a band of misfits seeking to shoot, loot, dodge roll and table-flip their way to personal absolution by reaching the legendary Gungeon’s ultimate treasure: the gun that can kill the past. Select a hero [or team up in co-op] and battle your way to the bottom of the Gungeon by surviving a challenging and evolving series of floors filled with the dangerously adorable Gundead and fearsome Gungeon bosses armed to the teeth. Gather precious loot, discover hidden secrets, and chat with opportunistic merchants and shopkeepers to purchase powerful items to gain an edge.

The Gungeon: Enter the Gungeon – a constantly evolving bullet hell fortress that elegantly blends meticulously hand-designed rooms within a procedurally-generated labyrinth bent on destroying all that enter its walls. But beware – the Gungeon responds to even the most modest victory against its sentries and traps by raising the stakes and the challenges found within!</desc>
		<image>./images/epic_EnterTheGrungeon-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/epic_EnterTheGrungeon-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/epic_EnterTheGrungeon-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<boxback>./images/epic_EnterTheGrungeon-boxback.png</boxback>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20160405T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Dodge Roll</developer>
		<publisher>Devolver Digital</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / 3ª persona</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<md5>d55926eec31ef35ab717a5c17c419257</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./epic_FallGuys.cmd</path>
		<name>Fall Guys: Ultimate Knockout</name>
		<thumbnail>./images/epic_FallGuys-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20200804T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Mediatonic</developer>
		<publisher>Devolver Digital</publisher>
		<genre>Party</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>dd35cb3dd090e5510e3f9305510fffb5</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game id="251495">
		<path>./epic_HorizonChaseTurbo.cmd</path>
		<name>Horizon Chase Turbo</name>
		<desc>Horizon Chase Turbo is a racing game inspired by the great hits of the 80's and 90's: Out Run, Lotus Turbo Challenge, Top Gear (SNES), Rush, among others. Each curve and each lap, in Horizon Chase Turbo recreates classic arcade gameplay and offers you unbound speed limits of fun. Full throttle on and enjoy!

With Multiplayer Split Screen support across all game modes, to rescue the nostalgia of playing with your best friends sitting on a couch all night long. The hard time is to know who is your best friend because this one is also the one to be beaten.</desc>
		<image>./images/epic_HorizonChaseTurbo-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/epic_HorizonChaseTurbo-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/epic_HorizonChaseTurbo-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<boxback>./images/epic_HorizonChaseTurbo-boxback.png</boxback>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20180515T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Aquiris Game Studio</developer>
		<publisher>Aquiris Game Studio</publisher>
		<genre>Carreras, Conducción / Carreras 3ª persona</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<md5>7bb09ddc44f3516404b40035af528995</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game id="273148">
		<path>./epic_TheAltoCollection.cmd</path>
		<name>The Alto Collection</name>
		<desc>The Alto Collection is a compilation of two games:
Alto's Adventure
Alto's Odyssey</desc>
		<image>./images/epic_TheAltoCollection-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/epic_TheAltoCollection-marquee.png</marquee>
		<boxback>./images/epic_TheAltoCollection-boxback.png</boxback>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20200813T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Snowman</developer>
		<publisher>Snowman</publisher>
		<genre>Compilación</genre>
		<md5>a30967951a74a7a845baeb702cec876f</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./pes6.exe.lnk</path>
		<name>Pro Evolution Soccer 2011</name>
		<desc>Pro Evolution Soccer 2011  is an association football video game in the Pro Evolution Soccer series developed and published by Konami with production assistance from the Blue Sky Team. The game was announced on 9 February 2010 and was released on the PlayStation 3, PC and Xbox 360 on 30 September 2010 in the European Union and 8 October 2010 in the United Kingdom. The versions of Wii, PlayStation 2, and PlayStation Portable were released on 28 October 2010. The UEFA Champions League and UEFA Europa League are featured within the game, and for the first time in the series, UEFA Super Cup and CONMEBOL's Copa Libertadores will be fully licensed</desc>
		<image>./images/pes6.exe-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20101008T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<hidden>true</hidden>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./ROJO-ASpanishHorrorExperience.lnk</path>
		<name>ROJO - A Spanish Horror Experience</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19700101T010000</releasedate>
		<md5>b9db8627f3ee78ac46f1d5d3319c4e5e</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SonicAllStarsRacingTransformed.lnk</path>
		<name>Sonic &amp; All-Stars Racing Transformed</name>
		<desc>Sonic and the All-Stars cast line up on the starting grid once again to battle for supremacy in the ultimate race. Compete across land, water and air in incredible transforming vehicles that change from cars to boats to planes mid-race. Master your driving skills as you drift, barrel role and boost to overtake your rivals, or use your weapons tactically and unleash your All-Star move to gain the winning advantage. It's not just your fellow racers you need to watch out for, as the road falls away beneath you, or the river runs dry, new routes emerge and your vehicle transforms to take advantage of the terrain. Discover alternative routes and short cuts as you perfect the course in this adrenaline fuelled dash to the finish line - racing will never be the same again. This is not just racing, it's racing transformed!</desc>
		<image>./images/SonicAllStarsRacingTransformed-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/SonicAllStarsRacingTransformed-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/SonicAllStarsRacingTransformed-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20130201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sumo Digital Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<md5>d7a8301e33032c7f42fe71f6cebd2eda</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SonicTimeTwisted.lnk</path>
		<name>Sonic Time Twisted</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19700101T010000</releasedate>
		<md5>18eee4c2c83df60748db89f17a61a57a</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game id="306838">
		<path>./steam_HoratioGoesSnowboarding.cmd</path>
		<name>Horatio Goes Snowboarding</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<md5>64ceda6fd2bb5b063bd8826fea3e2a8a</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./steam_nightsIntoDreams.cmd</path>
		<name>NiGHTS into Dreams...</name>
		<desc>Nights into Dreams... (ナイツ Naitsu?, written as NiGHTS into Dreams...) is an action game released by Sega in 1996 for the Sega Saturn video game system. The game's story follows two children entering a dream world, where they are aided by the titular main character, Nights. Nights was developed by Sonic Team, with Yuji Naka as producer and lead programmer, and Naoto Ōshima as the character designer and director. The developers' intention was to make the sensation of flight the central gameplay element</desc>
		<marquee>./images/steam_nightsIntoDreams-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/steam_nightsIntoDreams-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20121217T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure, Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<md5>b073ca14400a65d7016ce3e9028451b9</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game id="339840">
		<path>./steam_SonicCD.cmd</path>
		<name>Sonic CD</name>
		<desc>Rather than a straight port or an emulated title, this version of the 1993 Sonic CD game is a completely redone version for modern platforms and based on a fanmade Retro engine. The original version was released for the SEGA CD and later also ported to Windows. This version supports a whole host of more modern platforms as well as a complete re-release for the Windows platform.

It has many changes and additions, such as true 16:9 aspect ratio (instead of stretched 4:3 like the ports of other Sonic games), the choice between both the Japanese/European and American soundtracks, a constant framerate of 60 frames per second, several bugfixes, an option to select between the original CD's Spin Dash or the Sonic 2 Spin Dash and the inclusion of Tails (with his Sonic 3 abilities) as an unlockable character.

The game adds leaderboards for the Single Player and Time Attack modes. It also regains the original game's extra modes, the D.A. Garden and Visual Mode, and also includes the Sound Test and Stage Select modes as unlockables, unlike the original in which you had to input a cheat code to enter them.</desc>
		<image>./images/steam_SonicCD-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/steam_SonicCD-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/steam_SonicCD-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<boxback>./images/steam_SonicCD-boxback.png</boxback>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20120119T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Plataforma</genre>
		<family>Sonic</family>
		<md5>283b09c952d56d768c75be754ae3699d</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./steam_bayonetta.cmd</path>
		<name>Bayonetta</name>
		<desc>Bayonetta is an action game created by Hideki Kamiya. After 500 years of sleep, a witch named Bayonetta awakes and finds herself confronted by enemies. With no recollection of who she is or the reason she is being attacked, Bayonetta must battle her way through the city of Vigrid while her memory returns. 

Bayonetta can magically shape her hair into anything and uses it as a weapon to eliminate her enemies. She also has 4 guns at her disposal, two handguns and two attached to her heels. Bayonetta's guns are interchangeable with other weapons that are accessible throughout the game. Weapons can be bought or will be dropped by enemies defeated in battle, weapons bought can be upgraded but weapons dropped by enemies are only temporary.

The game features slow-motion in the form of Witch Time, which is activated with a well-timed dodge during battle. In this mode Bayonetta can counter-attack enemies before they have the chance to react.</desc>
		<image>./images/steam_bayonetta-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/steam_bayonetta-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/steam_bayonetta-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<boxback>./images/steam_bayonetta-boxback.png</boxback>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20170411T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Platinum Games</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Adventure / Survival Horror, Strategy</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220811T214124</lastplayed>
		<md5>146552dbdce172deb2dbb7bb2adeb1a5</md5>
		<gametime>33</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./gtaSanAndreas.lnk</path>
		<name>Grand Theft Auto: San Andreas</name>
		<desc>Grand Theft Auto: San Andreas is the fifth installment in the GTA series and takes place within the state San Andreas, which is based on sections of California &amp; Nevada. It comprises three major fictional cities: Los Santos corresponds to real-life Los Angeles; San Fierro corresponds to real-life San Francisco; and Las Venturas and the surrounding desert correspond to real-life Las Vegas and the Nevada and Arizona desert.</desc>
		<image>./images/gtaSanAndreas-image.jpg</image>
		<marquee>./images/gtaSanAndreas-marquee.png</marquee>
		<boxback>./images/gtaSanAndreas-boxback.jpg</boxback>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20050607T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rockstar North</developer>
		<publisher>Rockstar Games</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Role-Playing, Shooter, Life Simulation</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220814T234420</lastplayed>
		<gametime>19</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game id="316616">
		<path>./MalditaCastilla.lnk</path>
		<name>Maldita Castilla</name>
		<desc>The kingdom of Castile is cursed. Thou hath been sent forth by thy King to learn of the source of this evil and rid the land of it. God be with thee, Don Ramiro!

Maldita Castilla (Damn Castile) is a side scrolling action game that is, clearly, inspired by such games as Ghosts 'N Goblins, Rygar, Karnov, among others.

You, as Spanish knight Don Ramiro, must move to the right, killing enemies as you go. Along the way, you encounter treasure chests that will help you. At certain points, you must defeat a boss to advance. You are trying to get through all the bosses to find and defeat the source of all this evil plaguing Castile.</desc>
		<image>./images/MalditaCastilla-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/MalditaCastilla-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/MalditaCastilla-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<boxback>./images/MalditaCastilla-boxback.png</boxback>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20121212T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Locomalito</developer>
		<publisher>Locomalito</publisher>
		<genre>Acción</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220814T234205</lastplayed>
		<md5>387c0ffc31843c162c27c8c328c09cfa</md5>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./sonicTripleTrouble.lnk</path>
		<name>Sonic Triple Trouble 16-bits</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19700101T010000</releasedate>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220814T234352</lastplayed>
		<gametime>64</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game id="330850">
		<path>./uplay_RaymanOrigins.cmd</path>
		<name>Rayman Origins</name>
		<desc>During what appears to be a normal day, Rayman and his friends are chilling out on a giant tree in their homeland, the Glade of Dreams. Their constant snoring however disturbs an old granny from a land located in the depths below, the Land of the Livid Dead. Determined to put an end to the never ending noises she sends an army of evil creatures across the land, capturing all Electoons and Nymphs that populate the world in the process. As Rayman and his friends are captured from the creatures, they must flee their prison and attempt to bring order back to the Glade of Dreams before it's too late.</desc>
		<image>./images/uplay_RaymanOrigins-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/uplay_RaymanOrigins-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/uplay_RaymanOrigins-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<boxback>./images/uplay_RaymanOrigins-boxback.png</boxback>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20120329T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ubisoft</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Acción</genre>
		<family>Rayman</family>
		<playcount>4</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220814T234020</lastplayed>
		<md5>44cc3c9cfeffe83eb4e1508c2375e7c2</md5>
		<gametime>139</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game id="330848">
		<path>./uplay_RaymanLegends.cmd</path>
		<name>Rayman Legends</name>
		<desc>Rayman Legends retains the graphical style and most gameplay elements of Rayman Origins. Up to four players can simultaneously progress though side-scrolling levels defeating enemies and collecting Lums. In each level there is a number of teensies to rescue and that opens up new levels and worlds. All the powers from the previous game (wall-running, air gliding etc.) are available to the characters from the start, but some new gimmicks are added, for example the ability to fire projectiles in some levels.  Murfy the greenbottle appears in some levels to aid the players. With a press of a button he operates machinery, pokes bigger enemies and opens up passages for the characters. In some versions of the game the fifth player can control Murphy's movement.</desc>
		<image>./images/uplay_RaymanLegends-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/uplay_RaymanLegends-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/uplay_RaymanLegends-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<boxback>./images/uplay_RaymanLegends-boxback.png</boxback>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20130903T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ubisoft Montpellier</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<family>Rayman</family>
		<playcount>6</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220815T123119</lastplayed>
		<md5>772d9af04cb138c51ae5c7446f329cff</md5>
		<gametime>333</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game id="195797">
		<path>./minecraft.lnk</path>
		<name>Minecraft</name>
		<desc>Minecraft is a video game of the "sandbox" type (completely free construction) developed by the Swedish Markus Persson, A.K.A. Notch, then by the development studio Mojang. It is a universe composed of voxels and generated randomly, which incorporates a craft system focused on the exploitation and transformation of natural resources (mineralogical, fossil, animal and plant).</desc>
		<image>./images/minecraft-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/minecraft-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/minecraft-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<boxback>./images/minecraft-boxback.png</boxback>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20111118T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Mojang</developer>
		<publisher>Mojang</publisher>
		<genre>Simulación / Vida</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<playcount>4</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220815T144523</lastplayed>
		<md5>be2c031cd4773ba99041761439cb04ec</md5>
		<gametime>567</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game id="339870">
		<path>./epic_SonicMania.cmd</path>
		<name>Sonic Mania</name>
		<desc>Experience the ultimate celebration of past and future in Sonic Mania, an all-new 2D Sonic adventure running at a crisp 60FPS with stunning HD retro-style graphics. Multiple playable characters give you the ability to go explosively fast as Sonic, soar as Tails, or power through tough obstacles with Knuckles' brute strength. You can re-live the Sonic of the past with an exciting new twist on classic zones while fighting against new bosses and Dr. Eggman's evil robot army. Go head-to-head with players in Competition Mode or play in Co-Op Mode with a friend. Sonic Mania was developed by Christian Whitehead, Headcannon, and PagodaWest Games in collaboration with Sonic Team. Welcome to Sonic Mania</desc>
		<image>./images/epic_SonicMania-image.png</image>
		<marquee>./images/epic_SonicMania-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/epic_SonicMania-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<boxback>./images/epic_SonicMania-boxback.png</boxback>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20170829T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Headcannon</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Plataforma / Corre y Salta con deslizamiento</genre>
		<family>Sonic</family>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>3</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220903T153718</lastplayed>
		<md5>59f9da58480bc4b7ba7ddd353cba39af</md5>
		<gametime>1192</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./steam_SonicGenerations.cmd</path>
		<name>Sonic Generations Collection</name>
		<desc>Celebrate 20 years of Sonic in an all new adventure that delivers a definitive experience to Sonic fans new and old!</desc>
		<marquee>./images/steam_SonicGenerations-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/steam_SonicGenerations-thumb.jpg</thumbnail>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20111103T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sonic Team</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220829T142919</lastplayed>
		<md5>be6b4ef5f5d86adbcdfe60d150d0a14e</md5>
		<gametime>799</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sonic2DBlast.lnk</path>
		<name>Sonic 2D Blast</name>
		<desc>Sonic 3D Blast is a 3D Platformer game, developed by Traveller's Tales and published by Sega, which was released in 1997.</desc>
		<image>./images/Sonic2DBlast-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19970930T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Traveller's Tales Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<playcount>3</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220904T182121</lastplayed>
		<gametime>20</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
</gameList>
